const dayNineteenQuestions = [
  {
    question:
      "Man actions are determined by him without Allah’s knowledge, this is the belief (Aqeedah) of ………………",
    options: ["Jabariyah", "Qadriyah", "Qadariyah", "Mu’tazilah", "Khawarij"],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the full name of ‘Imam Mahdi’?",
    options: [
      "Gulam",
      "Muhammad bn ‘Abdullah",
      "‘Abdullah bn Muhammad",
      "Muhammad bn Muhammad",
      "‘Abdullah bn ‘Abdullah",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which Angel is in charge of inspiration?",
    options: [
      "Angel Israfil",
      "Angel Israil",
      "Angel Jibril",
      "Angel Mikail",
      "Angel Isma’i",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which was the first sect to deviate from the belief of Ahlu Sunnah wal jama’ah during the life of the Caliphs?",
    options: ["Jabariyah", "Qadriyah", "Qadariyah", "Mu’tazilah", "Khawarij"],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the sect that: - Introduced innovated facts, make it compulsory in the religion, call those who are against them Kafir (Disbliefers) and decreed that to kill them is allow. - Rejects leaders that rules in accordance with Quran. - The origin of rejecting Muslim Scholars is from them?",
    options: ["Jabariyah", "Qadriyah", "Qadariyah", "Mu’tazilah", "Khawarij"],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Which chapter of the Quran is described as 'Mother of Quran'?",
    options: [
      "Suratu Yasin",
      "Suratul Fatiah",
      "Suratul Ikhlas",
      "Suratul Mulk",
      "Suratul Muhmineen",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which chapter of the Quran mentioned the story of slanderer?",
    options: [
      "Suratun Nur",
      "Suratul Hajj",
      "Suratul Yusuph",
      "Suratul Hud",
      "Suratu Zumar",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which chapter of the Quran is described as 'heart of the Quran'?",
    options: [
      "Suratu Luqman",
      "Suratu Yasin",
      "Suratul Dhariyat",
      "Suratul Hadid",
      "Suratul Fatiah",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How many times was the name of Prophet Ayub (May the peace be upon him) mentioned in the Quran?",
    options: [
      "one time",
      "two times",
      "three times",
      "four times",
      "five times",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "The scripture revealed to Prophet Ibraheem (May the peace be upon him) was mentioned twice in the Quran, where are the two places?",
    options: [
      "Suratul A’la and Suratul Anbiyaa",
      "Suratul Shams and Suratul Qiyama",
      "Suratul A’la and Suratun Najm",
      "Suratul A’la and Suratu Ibraheem",
      "Suratus Shu’araa and Suratul Dukhan",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "…………is the addition word found in the hadith narrated by a reliable reporter that was not included in the same hadith narrated by another reliable reporter.",
    options: [
      "Aothaq",
      "Thiqah",
      "Ziyadatul Aothaq",
      "Ziyadatul Thiqah",
      "Ziyadah",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "…………is the hadith that each reporter (starting from the Prophet Muhammad (May the peace and blessing of Allaah be upon him)) at each stage of Isnad is found reporting the hadith using the same mode of transmission, the same remark, or act in a particular manner while reporting it.",
    options: [
      "Al Mudabbaj",
      "Riwayatul aqran",
      "Al Musalsal",
      "Al Ma’ruf",
      "Al Mahfuz",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "……...is the methodology of the expert scholars of hadith in assessing the narrations and sorting out the genuine from the weak and others.",
    options: [
      "Science of Hadith",
      "Study of narrator",
      "History of hadith",
      "Collection of hadith",
      "Study of narration",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "…………….is the book of hadith that the author arranged its hadiths in alphabetical order.",
    options: ["As Sunan", "Al Jami’", "Al Musnad", "Al Mu’jam", "Al Mustadrak"],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "……………… is the book of hadith that the author arranged its hadiths in the ordering of the books of fiqh.",
    options: ["As Sunan", "Al Jami’", "Al Musnad", "Al Mu’jam", "Al Mustadrak"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
];

export default dayNineteenQuestions;
